I'll go with him now.
我现在就和他一起去。
Someone is following you.
有人在跟踪你。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Go on.
你继续。
Zi Cheng.
Zi Cheng.
Why are you here?
你为什么来这里？
Why left quietly?
为何悄然离开？
You shouldn't have come.
你不应该来。
Didn't expect that
没想到如此
you are still cheating on me
你还是在欺骗我
You still work for spies.
你仍然为间谍工作。
You said you wanted to save me.
你说你想救我。
In fact, you just want to use me.
其实你只是想利用我而已。
I just want to live for myself now.
我现在只想为自己而活。
no.
不是。
Yao Yao.
Yao Yao.
Come back with me.
跟我回去。
You can't continue to make mistakes.
你不能再继续犯错误了。
Huang Zicheng.
Huang Zicheng.
This all must end.
这一切都必须结束。
Yao Yao.
Yao Yao.
Kill him and you'll be free.
杀了他之后你就自由了。
The survivors are back.
幸存者回来了。
Huang Zicheng.
Huang Zicheng.
Bangun, Huang Zicheng.
Bangun, Huang Zicheng.
Yaoyao has returned to the night fog.
瑶瑶已经回到了夜雾之中。
Where is Huang Zicheng?
黄子成呢？
He is resting upstairs.
他正在楼上休息。
Who asked him to chase him?
谁让他去追的？
He said it was Gao Tianyang
他说是高天阳
Gao Tianyang
Gao Tianyang
Tetapi Gao Tianyang
Tetapi Gao Tianyang
won't admit
不会承认
these brothers and sisters
这些兄弟姐妹
Director Qin, can we arrest him?
秦处长，我们可以逮捕他吗？
save.
节省。
you...
你...
Huang's nephew
黄氏侄子
Jinhai County National Security Bureau
金海县国家安全局
Gao Tianyang
Gao Tianyang
That
那
Can we talk outside?
我们可以到外面谈谈吗？
OK
好的。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Are there cigarettes?
有香烟吗？
No cigarettes.
没有香烟。
The sugar is still there
糖还在
this doesn't work for me
这对我来说没用
Even Huang can stop it
就连黄也能阻止
He is better than me.
他比我好。
I'm no match for him.
我不是他的对手。
Don't you want to defend yourself?
你不想为自己辩护吗？
is that useful?
有用吗？
my daughter's illness
我女儿的病
Not recovered yet.
还没痊愈。
I do not think so
我不这么认为
You came so quickly.
你来得真快。
Where was he today?
他今天去哪儿了？
nursing home.
疗养院。
Why did he go to a nursing home?
他为什么去养老院？
He brought food.
他送来食物。
Delivery
送外卖
Dad, I'm full.
爸爸，我吃饱了。
Already full
已经满了
OK
好的。
Let's give the injection.
我们来注射注射剂。
Mali.
马里。
Bear.
忍受。
Bian Nana.
边娜娜.
He is the son of the Doctor. side
他是博士的儿子。边
The doctor's son Byrne.
博士的儿子 拜恩。
He suffers from schizophrenia.
他患有精神分裂症。
this disease
这种病
Can only rely on imported drugs
只能依赖进口药品
This is imported.
这是进口的。
as far as I know,
据我所知，
This medicine is very expensive.
这种药很贵。
About
大约
One shot costs about 700,000
一针大约需要70万
Get injections at least twice a year.
每年至少注射两次。
maybe a spy
也许是间谍
Just grab this.
只要抓住这个。
Leave it to Bian Na.
交给卞娜吧。
Delivery of medicine as a condition.
送药作为条件。
[Received Ph.D. Byrne. ]
[获得博士。拜恩。]
and become their people
并成为他们的人民
Finally he appeared.
终于他出现了。
Indeed.
确实如此。
Semasa Huang Zicheng
Semasa Huang Zicheng
And Huang Zicheng attacked the network
而黄子成则攻击网络
They steal samples.
他们窃取样品。
That's their whole plan.
这就是他们的全部计划。
before he leaves,
在他离开之前，
Exchange samples.
交换样品。
don't let him
别让他
Go with samples.
与样品一起去。
understand.
理解。
I always feel
我总觉得
Hidden deep enough
隐藏的够深的
At least it can be postponed for a longer period of time.
至少可以推迟更长的时间。
Wait until my daughter gets sick
等我女儿病了
He will recover.
他会康复的。
You gave Huang the box of candy that he gave you
你给了黄给你的那盒糖
as a means of communication
作为传播手段
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
你是故意的，不是吗？
To protect identity.
为了保护身份。
Jiahui told me to do this.
佳慧告诉我这样做。
But you can't quit smoking.
但你无法戒烟。
and betrayed you.
并背叛了你。
half year ago,
半年前，
My daughter's condition is getting worse.
我女儿的病情越来越严重。
The hospital had given up hope.
医院已经放弃了希望。
but I can not
但我不能
they submit
他们提交
For my daughter.
为了我的女儿。
let me
让我
Research information B13
研究资料B13
give them.
给他们。
You are a researcher.
你是一名研究员。
You should know.
你应该知道。
The results fell into the hands of spies.
研究结果落入间谍手中。
and endanger the country.
并危害国家。
what is that?
那是什么？
No matter who it is for,
无论为了谁，
i shouldn't
我不应该
Because you do.
因为你这样做。
Not only do you let yourself down,
不仅让自己失望，
Even countries.
甚至国家。
you are right.
你是对的。
honestly,
诚实地，
I feel much more relaxed
我感到轻松多了
I feel much more relaxed.
我感到轻松多了。
Humans need to be responsible
人类需要有责任
For myself.
为了我自己。
This will happen gradually.
这将逐渐发生。
regret?
后悔？
I failed the country
我辜负了国家
and disappointing
和令人失望的
My lifelong dream.
我一生的梦想。
Now there is another chance
现在还有一次机会
can be avoided
可以避免
cause greater losses
造成更大损失
But this matter
但这件事
definitely need you
一定需要你
cooperate with us.
与我们合作。
Submit this USB research report
提交这份 USB 研究报告
for you.
给你。
The sample you stole
你偷来的样本
Already replaced by us.
已经被我们取代了。
Send this to him.
把这个发给他。
prove
证明
Correct sample received.
收到正确的样品。
Encik you.
恩西克你。
are you looking for me?
你在找我吗？
sit down.
坐下。
Test Results.
测试结果。
Same as experimental data
与实验数据相同
Byrne given by dr.
博士给出的 拜恩。
Sample is correct
样本正确
Congratulations Yao Yao
恭喜姚姚
Complete the task successfully
顺利完成任务
So the conditions you agreed to before
所以你之前答应的条件
Will it count?
会算吗？
Don't worry.
不用担心。
The reward has been sent to your account.
奖励已发送至您的帐户。
Go investigate.
去调查吧。
How does it feel
感觉如何
【With your own hands? 】
【用你自己的双手？】
I have no love.
我没有爱。
OK
好的。
You have completed your changes.
您已完成更改。
no longer
不再
The young girl from before.
之前那个年轻的女孩。
All this is because of you
这一切都是因为你们
Mr. Z really appreciates you.
Z先生真的很欣赏你。
hope you really are
希望你真的是
Join the agent game.
加入代理游戏。
Mr. Z is Zhu Zheri.
Z先生是朱哲日。
En. Zhou?
En. Zhou?
you will definitely meet
你一定会遇见
This is the most successful one
这是最成功的一次
most successful.
最成功的。
Thanks.
谢谢。
This is the most beautiful thing
这是最美的事
Since childhood.
从小时候起。
This is from Zhuo Zhe.
这是卓哲发来的。
I can't take you away.
我不能带你走。
But if I don't go
但如果我不去的话
They won't believe you.
他们不会相信你。
but i can't let you
但我不能让你
Take the risk.
冒这个风险。
The current situation is
目前的情况是
if i don't go
如果我不去的话
They won't believe you.
他们不会相信你。
if i leave
如果我走，
fell into their hands,
落入他们手中，
There is no happy ending.
没有好的结局。
How to do this?
这个怎么做？
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
You live here.
你住在这。
I'll find a way.
我会找到办法的。
I have a solution.
我有办法。
You can make spies trust you,
可以让间谍信任你，
I will not fall into their hands.
我不会落入他们的手中。
Is there any way?
有什么方法呢？
I became a dead man.
我成了一个死人。
dead?
死人？
this is your first time
这是你第一次
Compliment me formally.
正式地夸奖我。
When will we meet next?
我们下次什么时候见面？
I don't even know.
我什至不知道。
After all, you are dead.
毕竟，你已经死了。
You're not very good either.
你也不是很好。
criminal!
刑事！
I go first.
我先走了。
Sorry for causing trouble for you
给你添麻烦了
good
不错
There is some reluctance towards Huang.
对黄有些不情愿。
no problem
没有什么问题
What is explained?
解释了什么？
Not very cooperative so far
目前为止还不太配合
But there is still plenty of time.
但时间还很充裕。
I believe
我相信
Definitely open your mouth.
绝对可以张开嘴。
this is him
这就是他
It won't be difficult.
不会很难。
Don't teach me.
别教我。
You know him too well
你太了解他了
if you don't interrogate him
如果你不审问他
I absolutely can't show up
我绝对不能出现
The fisherman's plan
这位渔夫的计划
not over yet
尚未结束
The show needs to go on.
这部剧还需要继续。
The first time I met you,
第一次遇见你，
I think you
我觉得你
not flexible.
不灵活。
But the fact is,
但事实是，
you are a good actor
你是个好演员
Thanks.
谢谢。
Kak Yao Yao
Kak Yao Yao
Superior has been contacted
上级已联系
Embassies abroad.
驻外使馆。
As long as they are willing,
只要他们愿意，
They can be sent back home at any time
可以随时将他们送回国
Zicheng sana
Zicheng sana
Don't worry.
不用担心。
I'll take care of him for you.
我会替你照顾他。
Thanks.
谢谢。
this is my first time
这是我第一次
use this method
使用这个方法
Send someone to jail.
把某人送进监狱。
This is also the first time.
这也是第一次。
What's the plan?
计划是什么？
What's your plan?
你的计划是什么？
Ada.
艾达.
There is a breakfast stall nearby.
附近有一个早餐摊。
I heard it's really good.
我听说这真的很好。
After sending you in,
送你进去后，
I will try.
我会尝试。
After dinner, go home and sleep
吃完饭就回家睡觉
Is it that delicious?
有那么好吃吗？
There has been a queue since morning
从早上就开始排队了
Closes at ten o'clock.
十点钟关门。
OK
好的。
After I was released from prison,
我出狱后，
You can also take me to try it.
你也带我去尝试一下。
Aren't you very persistent?
你不是很坚持吗？
as long as you can
只要你可以
Fill your stomach?
填饱肚子吗？
I was just thinking
我刚在想
appropriate changes.
适当的改变。
Maybe that's not bad either.
或许这样也不错。
I will pick you up on launch day.
发布当天我会来接你。
If there is no task
如果没有任务的话
I happen to have time
我碰巧有时间
I took you out to eat.
我带你出去吃饭了。
OK
好的
This, this is an interview
这，这是采访
Or interrogation?
还是审讯？
Everything is possible.
一切皆有可能。
people like me
像我这样的人
Already collected a lot
已经收集了很多
Youth experienced.
经历过的青春。
if you don't want to
如果你不想的话
The loss is very small
损失很小
Ability is only one aspect
能力只是一方面
That's our field
那是我们领域的
in our field
在我们的领域
Must have.
一定有。
We want to see you now.
我们现在想见你。
How to convince us.
如何说服我们。
accept you
接受你
Me me first
我我先
I think this job is very fashionable
我觉得这份工作很时尚
certainly.
当然。
everyone wants to be
每个人都想成为
The hero who saves the world.
拯救世界的英雄。
but some people
但有些人
let me understand
让我明白
In order to realize this dream,
为了实现这个梦想，
First, you have to learn surrender and sacrifice.
首先，你要学会臣服和牺牲。
Get rid of personal interests and emotions.
摆脱个人兴趣和情感。
Any time.
任何时候。
willing
愿意
Be willing to sacrifice.
愿意牺牲。
That's what this job is about.
这就是这份工作的意义所在。
the most interesting.
最有趣的。
The most fashionable thing is not who you are
最时尚的不是你是谁
what got
得到了什么
for dreams and beliefs
为了梦想和信仰
Dreams and beliefs.
梦想和信念。
What are you willing to sacrifice?
你愿意牺牲什么？
I would like to remain anonymous.
我愿意匿名。
Do you think you succeeded?
你认为你成功了吗？
certainly.
当然。
if not,
如果不，
I won't appear in front of you.
我不会出现在你面前。
but i think you are
但我认为你是
Your behavior of chasing Yaoyao
你追瑶瑶的举动
The risk is too great
风险太大
You didn't get approval from your superiors
你没有得到上级的批准
Gao Tianyang has recognized me
高天阳已经认可我了
he is my boss
他是我的老板
But he said it was your idea.
但他说这是你的主意。
he didn't stop you
他没有阻止你
No, he still refuses to take responsibility
不，他还拒绝承担责任
He is not actually kind.
他其实并不善良。
I can only tell you
我只能告诉你
you are lucky
你很幸运
If you don't have a bulletproof vest
如果你没有防弹背心
Bulletproof vest for you
防弹背心送给你
you might
你可能会
Still lying in the hospital.
还躺在医院里。
of.
的。
I believe in Gao Tianyang
我相信高天阳
dan Yao Yao
dan Yao Yao
They trust me too.
他们也信任我。
This is possible
这个有可能
Our young agents
我们的青年经纪人
should be there
应该在那里
No, of course.
不，当然。
You are still very young.
你还很年轻。
Have you thought about your future plans?
有没有想过未来的计划？
I am leaving
我走了
I can't get into this class.
我进不了这个班。
What is the word?
词是什么？
Will the NSA accept me?
国安局接受我？
Is this a scam?
这是骗局吗？
Director Qin.
秦司长。
Can I join the National Security Bureau?
我可以进国安局吗？
Kamu dan Gao Tianyang
Kamu dan Gao Tianyang
completely different.
完全不同。
Of course, he is an ordinary weapon.
当然，他是一把普通的武器。
I'm the secret weapon.
我就是秘密武器。
current international disputes
现在国际争端
The situation is very complex.
情况非常复杂。
we need diversity
我们需要有多样性
solution
解决方案
correct
正确的
Kamu dan Gao Tianyang
Kamu dan Gao Tianyang
suddenly disappeared
突然失踪
Have you given your father an explanation?
你有给你父亲一个解释吗？
Mr. Huang is very busy.
黄先生很忙。
if i leave for a few years
如果我离开几年
He will be calm and collected.
他会镇定自若。
As a member of the national security family,
作为国家安全大家庭的一员，
they are very difficult
他们非常困难
difficult
很难
this is your attitude
这就是你的态度
Very irresponsible.
非常不负责任。
of.
的。
sorry.
对不起。
actually
实际上
I don't
我没有
With yellow.
与黄。
That...
那...
but what
但什么
It's Gao Tianyang
是高天阳
He ran faster
他跑得更快了
He has experience and knows how to cheat
他有经验，知道如何作弊
no
不是
He knew how to convince Huang.
他知道如何说服黄。
Say this
说这个
Anyway
反正
Huang must know.
黄肯定知道。
We all love him.
我们都爱他。
Please next time
请下次
Can do better.
可以做得更好。
really.
确实。
next time.
下次。
I join.
我加入。
Already accepted me
已经接受我了
What does acceptance mean?
接受是什么意思？
We said it was like a detention center.
我们说这就像一个拘留中心。
Huang Zicheng.
Huang Zicheng.
After approval by the superior organization,
经上级组织批准后，
Agree with you to join Guoan.
同意你加入国安。
Another year.
另一年。
Secret training.
秘密训练。
Are you ready?
已经准备好了吗？
of.
的。
Enjoy your coffee.
您的咖啡，请享用。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Please wait.
请稍候。
I have to go.
我得走了。
Can we meet again?
我们可以再见面吗？
you said.
你说的。
separate now
现在分开
for the future.
为将来。
There is no burden to be together.
在一起没有负担。
This is the mission of an agent.
这就是代理人的使命。
Read philosophy through the website
通过网站阅读哲学
China's.
中国的。
look.
看。
Zhu Zheyi.
朱哲一.
[Use reading website]
[使用阅读网站]
to foreign spy agencies
给外国间谍机构
To foreign spy agencies.
给外国间谍机构。
Everything is here.
一切都在这里。
that's right
这是正确的
Ready to shut down the network.
准备关网了。
Investigate thoroughly.
彻底调查。
understand.
理解。
Any questions?
有什么问题吗？
What is the problem?
有什么问题？
yes the problem is
是的，问题是
Oh my god.
天啊。
what happen?
发生什么事？
China in the game
游戏中的中国区
closure.
关闭。
we have tried our best
我们已经尽力了
try your best.
尽你所能。
Transfer important players
转移重要球员
to other areas.
到其他地区。
As long as Z is not exposed,
只要Z不暴露，
The game still has a chance to rise again
游戏仍有机会再次崛起
Zhou Zhe becomes Z’s scapegoat
周哲成为Z的替罪羊
Did he betray Z?
他背叛了Z吗
To protect yourself?
为了保护自己？
Try to shut up Zhuo Zhe.
试着让卓哲闭嘴。
Thank you for your efforts.
感谢你付出的努力。
Mining successful
挖掘成功
【Intelligence Organization】
【情报组织】
[Who is hiding in Zhenhai. ]
[谁躲在镇海。]
【Agent Game】
【代理游戏】
agent game
代理游戏
from China
来自中国
China's.
中国的。
This is not only
这不仅是
Kimhae National Security Bureau wins
金海国安局胜利
This is also
这也是
The victory of the national security system.
国家安全体系的胜利。
New Era.
新时代。
we must face
我们必须面对
Many new challenges.
许多新的挑战。
It's good to be young
年轻真好
Dare to invade
敢于入侵
Dare to do it
敢于去做
Dare to imagine
敢于想象
dare to try
敢于尝试
plum
李
Mr. and Miss Huang.
黄先生小姐。
Already arrived
已经到了
This side dish is quite fresh.
这道配菜相当新鲜。
How to sell leeks?
韭菜怎么卖？
seven pieces
七件
Go up again.
再上去。
you buy it
你买它
I will calculate it based on the original price.
我会按照原价计算。
No.
不。
I can't use you.
我不能利用你。
How much do you need.
需要多少。
Three pieces.
三块。
Mali.
马里。
Two cucumber stems.
两根黄瓜茎。
Seven dollars.
七块。
Why haven’t I seen it recently?
怎么最近没看到
There are two handsome men in your family
你家有两个英俊的男人
grown up
长大的
Can't control it anymore
再也无法控制
Already come a long way
已经走了很远的路
OK
好的。
Another eggplant.
另一个茄子。
Smile.
微笑。
4.5 yuan.
4.5元。
Well, how much?
嗯，多少钱？
The total is 34.5.
总计为34.5。
Ready.
准备好了。
To take advantage of.
好好把握。
However,
然而，
i must prepare
我必须准备
for them.
对于他们来说。
Something is hot.
有东西很热。
What if he comes back suddenly?
万一他突然回来怎么办？
that's right.
这是正确的。
goodbye.
再见。
OK
好的。
Long time no see, Xiao Hua.
好久不见，萧华。
Change other areas.
更改其他区域。
I'm still that cat
我还是那只猫
You are still so naughty.
你还是那么顽皮。
China area is closed.
中国区已关闭。
It's hard to get a new number
很难获得新号码
Dongshan rises again
东山再次崛起
Be sure to dress more happily
一定要穿得更开心
celebrate.
庆祝。
The information you want.
您想要的信息。
all of these
所有这些
more active players
更活跃的玩家
More active players.
更活跃的玩家。
Following China’s key regions,
继中国重点区域之后，
These players have changed
这些球员发生了变化
Already here
已来到这里
200 gold coins, thank you
200金币，谢谢
I've been killed.
我已经被杀了。
No message received
未收到信息
This is Mr. Z
这是Z先生
Isn't this Zhu Zheri?
这不是朱哲日吗？
of.
的。
I find it strange too.
我也觉得奇怪。
Looks like Zhu Zheri
长得像朱哲日
There are more secrets hidden.
还隐藏着更多的秘密。
didn't tell us
没有告诉我们
Who is Mr. Z?
Z先生是谁
I am
我是
Are you all so sure?
你们都这么确定吗？
This is decided by the National Security Agency.
这是国家安全局决定的。
I know you are not Z.
我知道你不是Z。
Z。
Z。
This is just a code.
这只是一个代码。
it can be anyone
它可以是任何人
Yaoyao once told me.
瑶瑶曾经告诉过我。
Z has a new plan
Z有新计划
The secret service is just the beginning
特工任务仅仅是开始
Agency mission
代理使命
This is not just an online game
这不仅仅是一个网络游戏
It's a world of agents
这是一个代理的世界
There will be more in the future
以后还会有
More and more young people
越来越多的年轻人
Enter this world.
进入这个世界。
as long as they are
只要他们是
Have enough curiosity.
有足够的好奇心。
So they became
于是他们就成为了
already become
已经成为
Agent World Players
代理世界的玩家
of.
的。
who cares
谁会关心
The information they stole?
他们窃取的信息？
All players will know
所有玩家都会知道
Enter this secret agent universe.
进入这个特工的宇宙。
It was a world without the concept of country
那是一个没有国家概念的世界
A world where only agents rule
一个只有代理人规则的世界
sounds good.
听起来不错。
It feels like there is a place
感觉好像有一个地方
Our seats.
我们的座位。
I thought you would feel it
我以为你会感觉到
I'm bragging
我在吹牛
If you speak big words,
如果你说大话，
He doesn't need to find a way
他不需要找到办法
Tell me to take you out.
告诉我带你出去。
who is he?
他是谁？
Z。
Z。